Division of Vertebrate Zoology Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
Division of Vertebrate Zoology Archives
1954-2014
VZAR.000001
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
16
4 file cabinets
Archives of the Division of Vertebrate Zoology
Division of Vertebrate Zoology, Yale Peabody Museum
Biographical Sketch
(not applicable)
Description of the Material
Archives of the YPM Division of Vertebrate Zoology
Yale University
- United States Expeditions, Series I
  Scope and Contents
  Field notes and catalogs from various collecting trips in the United States
  - Arizona Expedition. Fred Sibleys expedtion while on a family trip to Arizona., 1975; 000795
  - Arizona Expedition. Fred Sibleys expedtion to Arizona and a small part of Texas. Contains catalogs, maps, and itinerary., 1975; 000796
  - California Expedition. Copy of Fred Sibleys expedtion catalog from California., 1970; 000797
  - Colorado Expedition. Ken corbin, Charles Sibley, Peter Bottjer, Andy Ferguson, and Rollin Bauer's expedtition to Colorado and Nebraska. Contains maps, and expedition catalog. Copies also found under Nebraska., 1970; 000798
  - Colorado Expedition. Fred Sibley and Ken Corbin's expedtition to Colorado and Nebraska. Contains map and expedition catalog. Copies also found under Nebraska., 1974; 000799
  - Connecticut Expedition Prior to 1970. Miscellaneus expedition catalogs from Connecticut prior to 1970., 000800
  - Connecticut Expedition. Charles Sibley's Connecticut Expedition catalog mostly from Guilford and Madison., 1970; 000801
  - Connecticut Expedition. Fred Sibley and Noble Proctor's Connecticut Expedtition catalog specificaly from Durham Meadows and Seymour., 1971; 000802
  - Connecticut Expedition. J.A Spendelow Connecticut Expedtition catalog, includes some information on specimens collected in New Jersey., 1972; 000803
  - Connecticut Expedition. Connecticut Expedtition catalog from Durham Meadows., 1973; 000804
  - Connecticut Expedition. J. A. Spendelow and J. Wilson's Connecticut Expedtition catalogs., 1974; 000805
  - Connecticut Expedition. 5 seperate Connecticut Expedtition catalogs from F. Sibley, R.H. Barker, D,G, Wysham, E. Stevens and N. Wheelwright., 1975; 000806
  - Connecticut Expedition. Multiple Connecticut Expedtition catalogs from various collectors., 1976; 000807
  - Connecticut Expedition. Connecticut Expedtition catalogs, some include information on specimens from NewYork., 1977; 000808
  - Connecticut Expedition. Connecticut Expedtition catalogs., 1978; 000809
  - Connecticut Expedition. Connecticut Expedtition catalogs., 1979; 000810
  - Connecticut Expedition. Connecticut Expedtition catalog., 1980; 000811
  - Connecticut Expedition. Connecticut Expedtition catalog., 1981; 000812
  - Connecticut Expedition. Miscellaneous Connecticut Expedtition catalogs. Few contain informatoin from MA, RI, NH., 1986-1989; 000813
  - Eastern Expedition. Pennsylvania, Kentucky, Missouri, Nebraska., 1971; 000822
  - Maine Expedition. Brunswick, ME 1970. Winter Harbor, ME 1975., 1970, 1975; 000814
  - Maryland Expedition., 1975; 000815
  - Massachusetts Expedition., 1978; 000816
  - Nebraska Expedition. Charles Sibley, Ken Corbin, Peter Bottjer, Andy Ferguson, Rollin Bauer. Colorado/Nebraska 1970. See Colorado, 1970., 000817
  - Nebraska Expedition. Fred Sibley, Ken Corbin., 1974; 000818
  - New Mexico Expedition., 1974; 000819
  - Oklahoma., 000824
  - Texas Expedition., 1974; 000820
  - Texas Expedition. Originals in Arizona, 1975., 000821
  - Western Expedition. North Dakota, Montana, Washington, California., 1977; 000823
- International Expeditions, Series II
  Field notes and catalogs from various international collecting trips.
  - Africa., 000826
  - Argentina., 1960-1961; 000827
  - Australia., 1974; 000828
  - Australia., 000829
  - Bolivia. 35mm slides., 1956; 000831
  - Borneo. In 2 folders., 1976-1977; 000830
  - Brazil., 1968-1969; 000833
  - Brazil., 1968; 000832
  - Cameroon., 000834
  - Canada. Manitoba., 000835
  - Christmas Island., 1963-1964; 000836
  - Colombia., 1975-1976; 000837
  - Colombia., 1975-1976; 000838
  - Colombia., 1975-1976; 000839
  - Comoros Expedition., 1972; 000003
    - Photographs, Film, etc. Super 8 film documenting expedition and includes footage of live Latimeria., 1972; 000004
  - Costa Rica., 1984; 000840
  - Dominican Republic., 1972, 1978; 000841
  - Dominican Republic., 1976; 000842
  - Ecuador., 1930; 000843
  - Egypt-Nubia., 1962-1965; 000845
  - Egypt., 1975; 000844
  - Haiti., 1958; 000847
  - Honduras., 1973; 000848
  - India-Yale/Harvard Expedition., 000846
  - Kenya., 1963-1964; 000849
  - Kenya., 1965; 000850
  - Kenya., 1967; 000851
  - Laos., 000852
  - Madagascar., 000853
  - Malaya., 000854
  - Mexico., 1948-1951; 000855
  - Mexico., 1975; 000856
  - Micronesia., 1973; 000857
  - Miscellaneous. South Africa 1961/62, James Grace., 001433
  - New Guinea., 1954-1955; 000860
  - New Guinea. Alpha Helix, 2 folders., 1969; 000858
  - New Guinea. Alpha Helix, Aplonis list., 1969; 000859
  - New Zealand., 000861
  - Nigeria., 1974; 000862
  - Nigeria., 1975-1976; 000863
  - Norway., 1966; 000864
  - Pakistan., 1975; 000865
  - Panama., 1966; 000866
  - Peru., 1976; 000867
  - Philippines., 000868
  - Seychelles., 1957-1958; 000869
  - South Africa, Rhodesia., 1974; 000871
  - South Africa., 1976; 000870
  - Surinam., 1961; 000872
  - Taiwan., 1975; 000873
  - Thailand., 1975; 000874
- Egg Data Slips, Series III
  - Bishop Collection., 001284
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 673-701., 001285
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 848-859 Edwin S. Bryant. 1008-1011. 1013, 1016-1020, 1033-1037., 001286
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 1125-1127, 1148-1174., 001287
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 1185-1214., 001288
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 1251-1253, 1322-1236, 1535-1546.., 001289
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 1547-1556., 001290
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 1557-1561, 1724-1728, 1872-1875, 1880-1886, 1888-1890, 1892, 1893, 1896, 1913, 1919-1922.., 001291
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 1924-1957., 001292
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 2027-2039., 001293
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. Canfield Collection. 2132-2196.., 001294
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. Babbitt, Clayton, Raine Collections. 2197-2212, 2220-2234., 001295
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. Savavge Collection (1 of 2). 2235-2353., 001296
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. Savavge Collection (2 of 2). 2354-2461., 001297
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. H.W. Marsden Collection, 1905. 2557-2608., 001298
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 2621-2628, 2708-2760 Spaulding, Bodfish, Gordon, Snow., 001299
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 2864-2914, 2966-2996., 001300
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 2997-3007, 3009, 3012-3016, 3037-3050.., 001301
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. Meeker Collection. 3051-3082., 001302
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3090-3133 (plus a single egg, which preceds set #3090), 3136-3139., 001303
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3159-3175., 001304
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3176-3199, 3215., 001305
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. Robert S. Judd Collection. 3216-3240., 001306
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. Troup D. Perry Collection. 3241-3249., 001307
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3250-3262., 001308
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3266-3278., 001309
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3285, 3286, 3298, 3299., 001310
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3300-3335, 3337., 001311
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3338-3354., 001312
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3355-3375, 3378, 3379., 001313
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3282-3411, 3438-3442.., 001314
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3445-3479., 001315
    - Bishop Collection. Egg/Nest Sets. 3507-3518., 001316
  - Egg Data Slips - A., 000006
    - Acanthiza sp., 000032
    - Acrocepttalus., 000038
    - Alauda., 000053
    - American Black Duck., 000077
    - American Pipit., 000090
    - American Wigeon., 000069
    - Anhinga., 000079
    - Australian Brushturkey., 000056
    - Bairds Sparrow., 000060
    - Bean Goose., 000086
    - Bell's Sparrow., 000113
    - Black Noddy., 000080
    - Black-chinned Hummingbird., 000105
    - Black-throated Sparrow., 000067
    - Blue-winged Teal., 000073
    - Boreal Owl., 000043
    - Brown Noddy., 000081
    - Buff-Bellied Hummingbird., 000059
    - Burrowing Owl., 000118
    - California Scrub Jay., 000096
    - Canvasback., 000125
    - Chuck-Wills-Widow., 000093
    - Cinnamon Teal., 000072
    - Common Myna., 000037
    - Common Redpoll., 000030
    - Common Sandpiper., 000039
    - Cooper's Hawk., 000033
    - Crested Auklet., 000045
    - Daurian Starling., 000050
    - Dove Kie., 000057
    - Dusky Woodswallow., 000112
    - Eastern Whip-Poor-Will., 000094
    - Eurasian Teal., 000071
    - Eurasian wigeon., 000075
    - Florida Scrub-Jay., 000098
    - Gadwall., 000078
    - Golden Eagle., 000103
    - Grasshopper Sparrow., 000062
    - Gray Heron., 000108
    - Graylag Goose., 000083
    - Great Blue Heron., 000109
    - Great Egret., 000107
    - Great White-fronted Goose., 000082
    - Greater Scaup., 000124
    - Henslow's Sparrow., 000061
    - Hoary Redpoll., 000031
    - Island Scrub-Jay., 000099
    - Jungle Myna., 000036
    - LeConte's Thrasher. 548, 000064
    - Least Auklet., 000047
    - Lesser Scaup., 000120
    - Limpkin. Includes photograph of collecting site., 000104
    - Long-eared Owl., 000117
    - Mallard., 000076
    - Meadow Pipit., 000089
    - Mexican Jay., 000100
    - Mottled Duck., 000074
    - Nelson's Sparrow. Nelson's Sparrow, 000066
    - North Island Brown Kiwi., 000102
    - Northern Goshawk., 000034
    - Northern Pintail., 000068
    - Northern Saw-whet Owl., 000042
    - Northern Shoveler., 000070
    - Olive Sparrow., 000111
    - Parakeet Auklet., 000046
    - Pink-footed Goose., 000084
    - Razorbill., 000054
    - Red Avadavat., 000097
    - Red Wattlebird., 000087
    - Red-Winged Blackbird., 000048
    - Red-legged Partridge., 000055
    - Red-throated Pipit., 000088
    - Redhead., 000121
    - Ring-Necked Duck., 000122
    - Ruby-throated Hummingbird., 000106
    - Ruddy Turnstone., 000110
    - Rufous-crownded Sparrow., 000051
    - Sagebrush Sparrow., 000114
    - Saltmarsh Sparrow., 000063
    - Scaly-breasted Thrasher., 000058
    - Seaside Sparrow., 000065
    - Sharp-shinned Hawk., 000035
    - Short-eared Owl., 000116
    - Snow Goose., 000085
    - Southern Whiteface., 000095
    - Spotted Sandpiper., 000040
    - Sprague's Pipit., 000091
    - Tree Pipit., 000092
    - Tricolored Blackbird., 000049
    - Tufted Duck. Tufted Duck., 000123
    - Verdin., 000119
    - Western Grebe., 000041
    - White-Throated Swift., 000044
    - White-headed Marsh Tyrant., 000115
    - Wood Duck., 000052
    - Woodhouse's Scrub-Jay., 000101
  - Egg Data Slips - B., 000007
    - American Bittern., 000135
    - Barrow's Goldeneye., 000143
    - Black-crested Titmouse., 000126
    - Brant., 000136
    - Bridled Titmouse., 000130
    - Broad-Winged Hawk., 000150
    - Bufflehead., 000141
    - Bulwer's Petrel., 000144
    - Cackling Goose., 000138
    - Canada Goose., 000137
    - Cedar Waxwing., 000133
    - Common Black Hawk., 000153
    - Common Goldeneye., 000142
    - Ferruginous Hawk., 000151
    - Gray Hawk., 000149
    - Great Horned Owl., 000140
    - Green Heron., 000154
    - Juniper Titmouse., 000129
    - Oak Titmouse., 000128
    - Red-Shouldered Hawk., 000148
    - Red-Tailed Hawk., 000146
    - Rough-tailed Hawk., 000147
    - Ruffed Grouse., 000134
    - Snowy Owl., 000139
    - Swainson's Hawk., 000152
    - Tufted Titmouse., 000127
    - Upland Sandpiper., 000131
    - Xantus's Hummingbird., 000132
    - Zone-tailed Hawk., 000145
  - Egg Data Slips - C., 000008
    - American Crow., 000240
    - American Dipper., 000216
    - Anna's Hummingbird., 000172
    - Australian Magpie., 000248
    - Baird's Sandpiper., 000161
    - Banaquit., 000226
    - Black Guillemot., 000191
    - Black Tern., 000207
    - Black Vulture., 000238
    - Black-Billed Cuckoo., 000224
    - Blue Jay., 000256
    - Bonaparte's Gull., 000213
    - Broad-Billed Hummingbird., 000262
    - Brown Creeper., 000193
    - Buff-breasted Sandpiper., 000168
    - Cacomantis., 000155
    - Cactus Wren., 000174
    - California Quail., 000169
    - Canada Warbler., 000176
    - Canyon Wren., 000188
    - Carrion Crow., 000244
    - Chestnut-collared Longspur., 000158
    - Chihuahuan Raven., 000245
    - Chimney Swift., 000194
    - Chlorophonia., 000209
    - Cinnyris., 000217
    - Cisticola., 000219
    - Common Cuckoo., 000254
    - Common Ground-Dove., 000233
    - Common Nighthawk., 000212
    - Common Raven., 000242
    - Corn Crake., 000251
    - Costa's Hummingbird., 000173
    - Crested Caracara., 000175
    - Cyanistes., 000255
    - Dunlin., 000160
    - Eastern Wood-Pewee., 000237
    - European Goldfinch., 000181
    - European Goldfinch., 000182
    - European Greenfinch., 000208
    - Fish Crow., 000247
    - Gambel's Quail., 000170
    - Gilded Flicker., 000228
    - Golden Pheasant., 000214
    - Gray-Cheeked Thrush., 000186
    - Great Curassow., 000250
    - Greater Pewee., 000235
    - Greater Sage-Grouse., 000189
    - Green Jay., 000258
    - Grey Butcherbird., 000249
    - Grey Shrike-Thrush., 000230
    - Groove-Billed Ani., 000253
    - Hermit Thrush., 000185
    - Hooded Crow., 000243
    - Inca Dove., 000232
    - Killdeer., 000204
    - Lapland Longspur., 000157
    - Lark Bunting., 000156
    - Lark Sparrow. Lesser, 000210
    - Least Sandpiper., 000165
    - Lesser Nighthawk., 000211
    - Lesser Sand-Plover., 000200
    - Little Ringed Plover., 000197
    - Long-Tailed Duck., 000222
    - Mangrove Cuckoo., 000225
    - Marsh Wren., 000220
    - Montezuma Quail., 000264
    - Mountain Plover., 000201
    - Northern Bobwhite., 000229
    - Northern Cardinal., 000179
    - Northern Flicker., 000227
    - Northern Harrier., 000218
    - Northwestern Crow., 000241
    - Olive-Sided Flycatcher., 000234
    - Pectoral Sandpiper., 000164
    - Pigeon Guillemot., 000190
    - Piping Plover., 000199
    - Purple Sandpiper., 000163
    - Pyrrhuloxia., 000180
    - Red-faced Warbler., 000178
    - Rhinoceros Auklet., 000192
    - Ringed Plover., 000198
    - Rook., 000246
    - Ruff., 000166
    - Scaled Quail., 000171
    - Sedge Wren., 000221
    - Semipalmated Plover., 000203
    - Semipalmated Sandpiper., 000167
    - Smith's Longspur., 000159
    - Smooth-Billed Ani., 000252
    - Snowy Plover., 000202
    - Spotted Quail-Thrush., 000215
    - Steller's Jay., 000257
    - Stilt Sandpiper., 000162
    - Swainson's Thrush., 000187
    - Trumpeter Swan., 000259
    - Tundra Swan., 000260
    - Turkey Vulture., 000183
    - Vaux's Swift., 000195
    - Veery., 000184
    - Western Jackdaw., 000231
    - Western Wood-Pewee., 000236
    - White-Bellied Blue Flycatcher., 000263
    - White-Winged Chough., 000239
    - White-Winged Tern., 000206
    - Whooper Swan., 000261
    - Wilson's Plover., 000205
    - Wilson's Warbler., 000177
    - Wrentit., 000196
    - Yellow-Billed Cuckoo., 000223
  - Egg Data Slips - D., 000009
    - Ashy Drongo., 000269
    - Black-Bellied Whistling Duck., 000267
    - Bobolink., 000271
    - Dusky Grouse., 000266
    - Emu., 000272
    - Fulvous Whistling Duck., 000268
    - Gray Catbird., 000274
    - Pileated Woodpecker., 000273
    - Sooty Grouse., 000265
    - Wandering Albatross., 000270
  - Egg Data Slips - E., 000010
    - Acadian Flycatcher., 000290
    - Alder Flycatcher., 000282
    - American White Ibis., 000294
    - Brewer's Blackbird., 000297
    - Buff-Breasted Flycatcher., 000285
    - Dusky Flycatcher., 000288
    - Emberiza., 000281
    - European Robin., 000293
    - Hammond's Flycatcher., 000286
    - Horned Lark., 000292
    - Least Flycatcher., 000287
    - Little Blue Heron., 000276
    - Pacific-Slope Flycatcher., 000283
    - Passenger Pigeon., 000275
    - Reddish Egret. Reddish Egret, 000277
    - Rusty Blackbird., 000296
    - Scarlet Ibis., 000295
    - Snowy Egret., 000278
    - Tricolored Heron., 000279
    - White-Fronted Chat., 000291
    - White-Tailed Kite., 000280
    - Willow Flycatcher., 000289
    - Yellow-Bellied Flycatcher., 000284
  - Egg Data Slips - F., 000011
    - American Coot., 000311
    - American Kestrel., 000303
    - Aplomado Falcon., 000299
    - Atlantic Puffin., 000306
    - Common Chaffinch., 000310
    - Eurasian Coot., 000312
    - Eurasian Kestrel., 000304
    - Fluvicola., 000305
    - Gyrfalcon., 000302
    - Horned Puffin., 000308
    - Magnificent Frigatebird., 000309
    - Merlin., 000298
    - Northern Fulmar., 000313
    - Peregrine Falcon., 000301
    - Prairie Falcon., 000300
    - Tufted Puffin., 000307
  - Egg Data Slips - G., 000012
    - Arctic Loon., 000321
    - Common Gallinule., 000317
    - Common Loon., 000322
    - Common Moorhen., 000316
    - Common Snipe., 000315
    - Common Yellowthroat., 000330
    - Eurasian Jay., 000319
    - Ferruginous Pygmy-Owl., 000334
    - Gallus., 000318
    - Greater Roadrunner., 000326
    - Gull-Billed Tern., 000325
    - Kentucky Warbler., 000327
    - Key West Quail-Dove., 000331
    - Magpie-Lark., 000336
    - McGillivray's Warbler., 000329
    - Mourning Warbler., 000328
    - Northern Pygmy-Owl., 000335
    - Pacific Loon., 000323
    - Pinyon Jay., 000339
    - Red-Throated Loon., 000324
    - Ruddy Quail-Dove., 000332
    - Sandhill Crane., 000338
    - White-Tailed Hawk., 000333
    - Whooping Crane., 000337
    - Wilson's Snipe., 000314
    - Yellow-Billed Loon., 000320
  - Egg Data Slips - H., 000013
    - American Oystercatcher., 000342
    - Bald Eagle., 000347
    - Barn Swallow., 000352
    - Black Oystercatcher., 000340
    - Black-Necked Stilt., 000351
    - Caspian Tern., 000357
    - Cassin's Finch., 000343
    - Eurasian Oystercatcher., 000341
    - European Storm-Petrel., 000355
    - Evening Grosbeak., 000350
    - Harlequin Duck., 000353
    - Henicorhina., 000349
    - House Finch., 000344
    - Japanese Bush Warbler., 000354
    - Little Gull., 000356
    - Purple Finch., 000345
    - White-Tailed Eagle., 000346
    - Wood Thrush., 000358
    - Worm-Eating Warbler., 000348
  - Egg Data Slips - I., 000014
    - Audubon's Oriole., 000363
    - Baltimore Oriole., 000362
    - Bullock's Oriole., 000360
    - Hooded Oriole., 000361
    - Least Bittern., 000368
    - Mississippi Kite., 000367
    - Orchard Oriole., 000366
    - Scott's Oriole., 000365
    - Varied Thrush., 000369
    - Yellow Oriole., 000364
    - Yellow-Breasted Chat., 000359
  - Egg Data Slips - J., 000015
    - Dark-Eyed Junco., 000370
    - Yellow-Eyed Junco., 000371
  - Egg Data Slips - K., 000016
  - Egg Data Slips - L., 000017
    - American Herring Gull., 000392
    - Bar-Tailed Godwit., 000406
    - Black Rail., 000393
    - Black-Tailed Godwit., 000412
    - Brown Honeyeater., 000405
    - Brown Shrike., 000376
    - California Gull., 000381
    - Common Linnet., 000413
    - Franklin's Gull., 000403
    - Glaucous Gull., 000388
    - Glaucous-Winged Gull., 000385
    - Great Black-Backed Gull., 000389
    - Great Grey Shrike., 000377
    - Heermann's Gull., 000387
    - Herring Gull., 000380
    - Hooded Merganser., 000415
    - Hudsonian Godwit., 000411
    - Iceland Gull., 000386
    - Laughing Gull., 000402
    - Leiothrix., 000399
    - Lesser Black-Backed Gull., 000384
    - Leucosticte., 000404
    - Loggerhead Shrike., 000378
    - Lonchura., 000414
    - Long-Billed Dowitcher., 000408
    - Long-Tailed Shrike., 000379
    - Loxigilla., 000419
    - Lucy's Warbler., 000395
    - Luscinia., 000420
    - Lyrurus., 000421
    - Malleefowl., 000400
    - Marbled Godwit., 000410
    - Mew Gull., 000382
    - Nashville Warbler., 000397
    - Orange-Crowned Warbler., 000394
    - Red Crossbill., 000417
    - Red-Backed Shrike., 000375
    - Ring-Billed Gull., 000383
    - Rock Ptarmigan., 000374
    - Short-Backed Dowitcher., 000407
    - Silver Pheasant., 000416
    - Slaty-Backed Gull., 000391
    - Swainson's Warbler., 000409
    - Tennessee Warbler., 000396
    - Virginia's Warbler., 000398
    - Western Gull., 000390
    - White-Tailed Ptarmigan., 000373
    - White-Tipped Dove., 000401
    - White-Winged Crossbill., 000418
    - Willow Ptarmigan., 000372
  - Egg Data Slips - M., 000018
    - Abert's Towhee., 000443
    - Acorn Woodpecker., 000431
    - Ash-Throated Flycatcher., 000460
    - Belted Kingfisher., 000424
    - Black Scoter., 000434
    - Black-and-White Warbler., 000450
    - Bronzed Cowbird., 000451
    - Brown-Crested Flycatcher., 000462
    - Brown-Headed Cowbird., 000452
    - California Towhee., 000444
    - Canyon Towhee., 000445
    - Common Merganser., 000446
    - Common Scoter., 000437
    - Eastern Screech Owl., 000426
    - Eastern Yellow Wagtail., 000456
    - Elf Owl., 000448
    - Gila Woodpecker., 000433
    - Golden-Fronted Woodpecker., 000428
    - Great Crested Flycatcher., 000461
    - Lewis's Woodpecker., 000432
    - Lincoln's Sparrow., 000441
    - Megapodius., 000425
    - Myophonus., 000466
    - Northern Gannet., 000453
    - Northern Mockingbird., 000449
    - Painted Redstart., 000463
    - Red-Bellied Woodpecker., 000429
    - Red-Breasted Merganser., 000447
    - Red-Headed Woodpecker., 000430
    - Social Flycatcher., 000465
    - Song Sparrow., 000442
    - Southern Giant Petrel., 000422
    - Spotted Flycatcher., 000457
    - Sulphur-Bellied Flycatcher., 000464
    - Superb Fairywren., 000423
    - Surf Scoter., 000438
    - Swamp Sparrow., 000440
    - Townsend's Solitaire., 000458
    - Velvet Scoter., 000436
    - Western Screech Owl., 000427
    - White Wagtail., 000454
    - White-Winged Scoter., 000435
    - Wild Turkey., 000439
    - Wood Stork., 000459
    - Yellow Wagtail., 000455
  - Egg Data Slips - N., 000019
    - Black-Crowned Night-Heron., 000473
    - Common Pauraque., 000474
    - Eurasian Curlew., 000469
    - Helmeted Guineafowl., 000471
    - Long-Billed Curlew., 000468
    - Red-Crested Pochard., 000467
    - Whimbrel., 000470
    - Yellow-Crowned Night-Heron., 000472
  - Egg Data Slips - O., 000020
    - Aleutian Tern., 000483
    - Ashy Storm-Petrel., 000478
    - Band-Rumped Storm-Petrel., 000476
    - Black Storm-Petrel., 000480
    - Bridled Tern., 000484
    - Connecticut Warbler., 000486
    - Fork-Tailed Storm-Petrel., 000477
    - Leach's Storm Petrel., 000479
    - Least Storm-Petrel., 000481
    - Mountain Quail., 000487
    - Northern Wheatear., 000482
    - Plain Chachalaca., 000489
    - Ruddy Duck., 000490
    - Sage Thrasher., 000488
    - Sooty Tern., 000485
    - Wilson's Storm-Petrel., 000475
  - Egg Data Slips - P., 000021
    - American Flamingo., 000540
    - American Golden-Plover., 000574
    - American White Pelican., 000511
    - Arizona Woodpecker., 000549
    - Audubon's Shearwater., 000604
    - Bachman's Sparrow., 000517
    - Band-Tailed Pigeon., 000507
    - Black-Bellied Plover., 000575
    - Black-Capped Chickadee., 000580
    - Black-Footed Albatross., 000537
    - Black-Headed Grosbeak., 000535
    - Black-Headed Woodpecker., 000548
    - Black-Tailed Gnatcatcher., 000588
    - Black-Vented Shearwater., 000605
    - Blue Grosebeak., 000503
    - Blue-Gray Gnatcatcher., 000586
    - Boreal Chickadee., 000584
    - Brandt's Cormorant., 000527
    - Brown Pelican., 000512
    - Bushtit., 000598
    - California Gnatcatcher., 000587
    - Carolina Chickadee., 000581
    - Cassin's Auklet., 000600
    - Cassin's Sparrow., 000518
    - Chestnut-Backed Chickadee., 000585
    - Chiming Wedgebill., 000599
    - Cliff Swallow., 000516
    - Common Poorwill., 000529
    - Double-Crested Cormorant., 000523